Alex Earley

http://devearley.github.io/

5700 NW 2nd Ave Boca Raton, FL 33487 (561) 324-6988 AlexEarley@me.com

Summary

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER WITH A BACKGROUND IN MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT, ENTERPRISE WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT, AND EMAIL MARKETING CAMPAIGNS. PROFICIENT WITH C# OR PHP WEB SERVICES. OVER 10 YEARS EXPERIENCE WITH HTML, CSS, JS FOR FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT. ALEX IS A HIGHLY MOTIVATED INDIVIDUAL WITH AN ENTREPRENEURIAL SPIRIT.

Experience

Crossmatch

Full-Stack Developer - July 2017 to Present

- → Created UI mockups and prototypes in Figma
- → Built multiple frontends with AngularJS and SCSS
- → Implemented End to End testing with Protractor
- → Designed Restful API with Nancy and ORM with Dapper
- → Employed Domain Driven Design
- → Integrated Google reCaptcha and Google OpenID

Jet Marketing

Design and Development - August 2016 to October 2016

- → Created UI mockups in Photoshop
- → Built multiple frontends with angularJS and custom CSS
- → Interfaced with existing backend and services with PHP
- → Integrated with xVerify email verification and 'pixel' tracking services

eCannex.com

Senior Developer, Founder - July 2015 to Present

- → Built a frontend on angularJS and Material design by google
- → Built backend using C#, .NET, Dapper, WebAPI, and MSSQL

G.L. Homes

Developer - July 2013 to April 2016

- → Worked on enterprise software for managing construction schedules, integrating Microsoft Project with Aspose for .NET
- → Built interface for JD Edwards services
- → Built interactive 4K touch enabled video wall for The Bridges sales center using angularJS and CSS.
- → Built CRM customizations using javascript and angularJS
- → Designed interface for managing construction schedules using AngularJS, Bootstrap and CSS

Ultimate Software

Tech Star Intern - August 2011 to January 2012

- → Worked primarily on classic ASP to ASP.NET migrations
- → Built custom functionality for individual clients using javascript, jQuery, and ASP.NET

OneUp Games

Developer - May 2011 - August 2011

- → Published iOS App, Baseball Connect
- → Built prototype app in Objective-c using Cocos2d game framework.
- → Migrated prototype to native cocoa app

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Florida Atlantic University, Graduated in summer 2013